Jongik Jeon, Tangible interaction designer

South Korea, +82 10 8553 4698, matjisloth@gmail.com

Profile	I am an ideator and maker, de	lying into the fields of tand	ible interface, novel interaction

and auditory experience. I specialize in harnessing new technologies and transforming

futuristic ideas into real-world applications.

Links Personal website LinkedIn

Education

Mar 2017 — Feb 2024 Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), South Korea

Industrial design & Culture technology

Jan 2020 — Mar 2020 KTH Royal Institute of Technology, Sweden

Industrial design (exchange student)

Research

Jan 2023 — Present Affective Systems and Cognition Lab KAIST, South Korea

Novel sound interaction system by spraying sound in the air

Jun 2023 — Present DLX Design Lab University of Tokyo, Japan

Robotic in-car accessory for semi-autonomous vehicles

Mar 2022 — Dec 2022 SketchLab KAIST, South Korea

Al diary that plays emotion-responsive music

Jan 2022 — Mar 2022 Music and Audio Computing Lab KAIST, South Korea

Automatic emotional classification of video game music

Publications

Oct 2023 SoundMist: Novel Interface for Spatial Auditory Experience UIST '23 Poster

Jongik Jeon, Chang Hee Lee

Dec 2022 YM2413-MDB: A Multi-Instrumental FM Video Game ISMIR '22

Music Dataset with Emotion Annotations

Eunjin Choi, Yoonjin Chung, Seolhee Lee, Jonglk Jeon, Taegyun Kwon, Juhan Nam

Skills Physical computing; Rapid prototyping; Audio processing

Softwares: Fusion 360, Figma, Illustrator, Corel Draw, Praat, Logic Pro Coding languages: Python, Javascript, Java, Arduino, Processing, p5js, ChucK

Project management; User research; Design thinking; Ideation

Experiences

Jul 2019 — Present Fabrication lab technician

Managing digital fabrication equipments in fabrication facility

Mar 2022 — Dec 2022 Exhibition coordinator

Coordinating the design exhibition in Dongdaemun Design Plaza

Jul 2020 — Jan 2022 Republic of Korea Marine Corps.

Operating vulcan cannon, as a soldier under military service

Awards

Nov 2023 KAIST Q-day Special Award

Mar 2023 College of Engineering Leadership Award

Dec 2022 Graduation exhibition Excellence Award

Jul 2022 KAIST-ICL Hackathon Runner-up

Jul 2021 Best Military Cultural Innovation Idea

Jan 2020 KAIST Alumni Scholarship

Dec 2019 Dean's List

Languages English fluent Japanese basic Korean native